

NATALLIA PAPOVA

Junior QA Engineer

My name is Natallia. I would like to get a position as a Junior QA engineer. I completed the courses "Introduction to Software Testing" at EPAM Systems Inc. and "Software Testing" at Stormnet Technologies LLC. I have a degree in economics and experience in the banking sector as a specialist in settlement and cash services, as well as lending to legal entities. At the moment I am working as a chief accountant and working to improve my skills

breathby@gmail.com
+375295572450
Minsk, Belarus
linkedin.com/in/natallia-papova-4a199a208
https://join.skype.com/invite/JsW2dzjhr3bK(Skype)

Experience

Chief Accountant

UPSTYRIS LLC

2019 - Present

Belarus

- · Accounting, tax calculation and documentation analysis
- · Preparation of accounting and tax reports
- Analysis of changes in legislation
- · Personnel documents
- Development and compilation of internal local documents
- · Communication with suppliers and employees

Accountant

Armatrade-Uruchye LLC

2012 - 2019

Belarus

- Accounting
- Preparation of accounting and tax reports
- Preparation of accounting and personnel documents

Chief Specialist of the Active Operations Department of the Corporate Business Center Belarusbank

Belarusbank

2008 - 2009

Belarus

- Analysis of legal and financial documentation
- Analysis of the creditworthiness of the borrower and the collateral
- Preparation of credit documents (conclusion, contract, statements, etc.)
- · Communication with business clients
- Loan support

Specialist in settlement and cash services for legal entities

Belarusbank

2006 - 2008

Belarus

- · Service and communication with business clients
- · Conducting non-cash payments in different currencies
- · Conducting international transfers

Education

Software Testing

Stormnet Technologies LLC

2022 - 2022

Software Testing Course

Software Testing

Training Center EPAM Systems Inc

2021 - 2021

Software Testing Introduction Course

Finance and Credit

Belarusian State Economic University

2006 - 2011

Faculty of Finance and Banking

Banking

Minsk College of Finance and Economics

2003 - 2006

Languages

English - A2

Russian - Native Speaker

Soft Skills

Reliability Self-motivation Attention to detail

Analytical thinking Teamwork Communication skills

Technical Skills

Testing documentation (Test Planning, Checklist, Test Cases, Defect Report, Test result report)

Manual Testing (API Testing, Web Testing, Mobile Testing)

SQL (tables creation, data amending, data queries)

Postman, Jira Agile, Scrum Reporting & Analysis

Data exchange text formats: JSON and XML

HTTP requests - (GET, POST, PUT, DELETE)